{"data":[{"question":"The mouse was lucky that it just missed ___ .","a":"to be caught","b":"catching","c":"to catch","d":"being caught","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Miss + Verb_ing \n- Passive voice: Miss + being PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Jason would not be allowed ___ across the red line.","a":"risking to go","b":"to risk going","c":"risk going","d":"for risk to go","answer":"2","explain":"\n- This sentence can be rewrite as: Someone would allow Jason to risk going across the red line \n- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + Verb_ing \n- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + object + to V ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Jessica didn't remember ___ the captain before.","a":"have met","b":"having met","c":"to having met","d":"to meet","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Remember+ V_ing: Remember something which have already happened\/done \n- Remember+ To Verb: Remeber to do something (need to be done)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ , I went to the terminal to pick up one of my cousins.","a":"After eating quickly my lunch","b":"After my quickly eating lunch","c":"After eating my lunch quickly","d":"After eating my quickly lunch","answer":"4","explain":"\n- After + Verb-ing + Object: Play a role as an adverb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I make a apology for ___ ahead of time. \"That's all right.\"","a":"not letting you know","b":"letting you not know","c":"letting not you know","d":"letting you know not","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Apology for doing something \n- Let somebody do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The boy wanted to ride his bicycle in the street, but his father told him ___.","a":"not to do","b":"not to","c":"do not to","d":"not do it","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tell sbd (not) to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Please tell your friend ___ the laws.","a":"not to violate","b":"to violate not","c":"not violate","d":"to not violate","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tell sbd (not) to do sth ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Though Joe often made his little brother ___, today he was made ___ by his little brother.","a":"crying, crying","b":"cry, to cry","c":"to cry, cry","d":"cry, cry","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Make sbd do sth \n- Passive: be made to verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Our troops would not allow Edward ___ across the enemy line.","a":"risking to go","b":"to risk going","c":"risk going","d":"for risk to go","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + Verb_ing \n- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + object + to V","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"My relatives knew my daughter very well. They had seen her ___ up from childhood.","a":"grew","b":"grow","c":"to grow","d":"was growing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}